好的，现在我们有个艰巨的任务了。把
All right, here's a big one. Finish
SynchAdapter 完成，用它来获取天气数据，
the SynchAdapter, making it fetch the weather
并且储存在数据库中。在ForecastFragment中
and store it in the database. Alter
需要修改updateWeather函数，来与SyncAdapter
the updateWeather function within the ForecastFragment to
进行同步处理。这里需要注意一些，把onHandleIntent方法的代码放进
start a sync with the SyncAdapter. Some things here. Pull the code from on
SyncAdapter中。onHandleIntent方法的代码是
handle intent into our SyncAdapter. On handle
在我们的Sunshine服务里的。
intent is inside of our Sunshine service.
这样做的好处是虚拟分配同步adapter线程
The good news is that abstract threaded
会提供一个后台线程，来处理
sync adapter provides a background thread to
从服务器端获取的数据，就像是
run the server fetch on, just like
Intent服务一样。 同时会从utility类中
intent service does. Also, just fetch the location
获取位置数据。最终，我们
query from our utility class. Eventually, we
的目的是在无用户参与的情况下进行同步操作
want to run syncs like this without any
最终，同步adaptor会在我们
involvement of the user. Finally, make the
调用Update Weather之后运行。
sync adaptor run when we call Update Weather.